exemplum.com 2007-08-09

# Exemplum: Privacy Policy

**Legal Information**

Exemplum is an assumed name of Exemplum, Incorporated. 

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy is designed to assist you in understanding how this web site collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you provide to Exemplum. 

**What information does the site collect and how do we use it?**

When you visit this site you may provide Exemplum with two types of information: personal information you actively choose to disclose ("Active Information") through contacting Exemplum, and use information collected, in a way not visible to you, on an aggregate anonymous basis as you and others browse this site ("Passive Information"). 

Active information: 

If you wish to contact us, request a consultation, submit a quote, or obtain support. Exemplum collects your name, address, phone number, and email information. Personal information is not shared with outside parties and is used to: 

  * To deliver products and/or services that you request or purchase. 
  * To help us create and publish content most relevant to you. 
  * To alert you to new products or services, special offers, or updated information if you so request. 
  * To allow you access to limited-entry areas of our site as appropriate. 

Passive information: 

Our site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" to collect information about how this site is used. Passive Information gathered might include the date and time of visits, the site pages viewed, time spent at this site, the sites visited just before and just after this site. Passive Information is collected on an aggregate basis without any association to your personal information so that you remain anonymous. If you do not wish to transmit "cookie" information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser; please consult the "Help" section of your browser to correctly do so. If you choose to not use Cookies, some of the functionality of the website will be lost. 

We use Passive Information to learn more about our users and enhance their web site experience. Additionally, cookies help Exemplum know information about how many people visit this site, when they visit and how they use this site. We do not connect any of this information to your personal information or email address. 

**What is a Cookie?**

Cookies are a feature of web browser (Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator, etc.) software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a site. They are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's web browser on one site to simplify subsequent interactions with that site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transaction on related web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from site to site and to complete transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized. 

**How do we secure information?**

We secure your personal information submitted by you by using reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of Active Information and Passive Information. All data is stored on servers at Exemplum. 

**How can you change or delete your personal information?**

If you desire not to receive information or if you wish to access, delete or correct your information, please send Exemplum an email to [info@exemplum.com](mailto:info@exemplum.com). 

We reserve the right to revise this policy at our discretion. Please check back on this site as this policy may be revised from time to time without notice to you.
